六块钱
Six dollars,please.
六块？我才租了一个晚上 是三块钱
Six? I just had it for one night. It's three.
八点钟结算，现在八点两分了
Eight o'clock's the cutoff. And,oh,it's 8:02.
不知道为什么 你的权力好像太大了
You know,in a weird way,you have too much power.
你得帮帮我，我只有三块钱
You have to help me because I only have three.
我可以帮忙
I can help with that.
我的天，理查？
Oh,my God. Richard?
你的胡子刮掉了
Your lip went bald.
谢谢
Thanks.
你气色很好
You look great!
是啊
Right.
不，真的，你…
No,you do. You....
什么？
What?
你的内裤黏在腿上了
You got panties stuck to your leg.
我刚才从烘干机里 拿出衣服，这是静电
I was just grabbing some things out of the dryer,and static cling.
也许老天爷知道我会碰到你 觉得这是个机会
Or maybe God knew I'd be running into you and saw an opportunity.
见到你真高兴
It's good to see you.
我也是
It's good to see you too.
本集播出： “莫妮卡与查理成为朋友”
The One Where Monica and Rich are Just Friends
（成人片区）看到那家伙没有？ 他现在看的是经典巨片
See that guy? He's in "Classics" now...
不过等我们一走 他就马上去逛色情片
... but as soon as we leave,he's going straight to the porn.
到时候他会租“公民凯恩” “迷魂记”和“发条纵欲”（模仿《发条橙》）
He'll go to the counter with Citizen Kane,Vertigo and Clockwork Orgy.
这样真好
This is nice.
我好怀念这种时光 我也是
-I miss this. -Me too.
很抱歉，我们还要在这里待久一会儿，所以你直接去那里就行了
Excuse me.We're gonna be here for a while,so just go back there.
是的，我们还没决定好
Yeah, we're not judging.
想一起吃个汉堡什么的吗？
You want to get a hamburger or something?
我不知道这样好不好
I don't know if that's a good idea.
只是朋友嘛 我保证不会毛手毛脚
Just friends. I won't grope you. I promise.
我觉得太快了
I think it's too soon.
不会太快，我十一点吃的午餐
No,it's not too soon. I had lunch at 11.
好啊
Yeah,baby!
你在做什么？ 巧克力牛奶，想喝吗？
-What are you making? -Chocolate milk. Want some?
不，谢了，我已经29岁了
No,thanks. I'm 29.
我的天，我得上班了
Oh,my God! I gotta go to work!
你今晚几点下班？
What time will you get off tonight?
可能会很晚
It could be really late.
拜托，怎么又这样？
Not again!
我知道，对不起 我们商量一下好吗？
I know. I'm sorry. I'll make a deal with you,okay?
只要你在我回家以前睡着…
Every night that you're asleep before I get home...
我就用你以前 很喜欢的方法把你唤醒
... I will wake you up in a way that has proved popular in the past.
如果你要加班 我很愿意支持你
Well,if you need to stay late,I want to be supportive of that.
看，你什么时候开始溜冰了？
Look at you. Since when do you rollerblade?
明天
Since tomorrow.
我在公园遇到一个帅哥
I met a cute guy in the park.
他是慢跑、溜冰和 游泳高手，我们说好了
And he jogs and blades and swims and so we made a deal.
他要教我各种运动
He's gonna teach me how to do jock stuff.
那你要如何回报他？ 我会让他达到目的
-And what are you gonna do for him? -I'm gonna let him.
很好
Cool.
早安
Good morning.
有人昨晚很晚才回来哦
Somebody got in late last night.
这个嘛，我碰到理查了
Yeah,well,I ran into Richard.
什么时候的事？
When did this happen?
大概八点零二分
Around 8:02.
我们聊了一会儿 然后一起吃了个单纯的汉堡
We talked for a while,and then we went out for an innocent burger.
没有所谓“单纯的汉堡”
There's no such thing as an "innocent burger."
你还会跟他见面吗？ 明天晚上
-Gonna see him again? -Tomorrow night.
莫妮卡，你这是在干什么？
Monica,what are you doing?
她花了六个月才忘记他…
She spent six months getting over him...
现在她庆祝的方式 就是跟他约会
...and now she's celebrating that by going on a date with him.
这不是约会，好吗？
It's not a date,okay?
我要教他做意大利面 他要在家里请客
I'm teaching him how to make a lasagna for a potluck dinner.
最好多做一点 做爱之后会很饿
You might want to make extra,because you'll be hungry after the sex.
我们不会上床
We're not gonna have sex.
一切如旧，他还是不要孩子 我还是想要孩子
Nothing's changed here. He still doesn't want children,and I still do.
所以我们只能当朋友
So we're just gonna be friends.
赤裸的朋友
Naked friends.
你有冰吗？ 打开冰箱看看
-Do you have any ice? -Check the freezer.
如果没有，那大概就是用完了
If there's none in there,we're probably out.
你刚下班吗？很晚了
Are you just getting home? It's late.
我知道，不过今天实在太棒了
I know. I had the greatest day,though.
我和卡文克莱的销售代表开会
I went to a meeting with reps from Calvin Klein.
我看中一款性感内衣 我老板就订了一吨，你呢？
I liked a line of lingerie,so my boss ordered a ton of it. And you?
我发现我可以 光用舌头数完所有牙齿
I discovered I'm able to count all my teeth using just my tongue.
你把一本“闪灵” 放在冰箱干嘛？
Why do you have a copy of The Shining in your freezer?
我昨晚越看越害怕，就…
I was reading it last night and I got scared,so....
把书放进冰箱 你就安全了吗？
But you're safe from it if it's in the freezer?
至少安全一点
Well,safer.
我每次看书的时候…
I never start reading it...
都先确定冰箱里有地方放…
...without making sure we got room in the freezer.
你常常看这本书吗？
How often do you read it?
你从不把一本书一看再看吗？
Haven't you ever read a book over and over again?
“小妇人”我看了好几次
I read Little Women more than once.
那是经典作品 “闪灵”哪里好看？
It's a classic. What's so great about The Shining?
你应该问 “闪灵”有哪里不好看
The question should be,what is not so great about The Shining?
答案是“没有”，知道吗？
And the answer would be,"nothing." All right?
这是有史以来最恐怖的书
This is the scariest book ever.
一定比你的经典作品好看
I bet it's better than that classic of yours.
我们走着瞧，好吗？
We'll just see about that,okay?
我看“闪灵” 你看“小妇人”
I will read The Shining,and you will read Little Women.
好，没问题
All right,you got it.
瑞秋，这些小妇人
Now,Rach,these little women....
到底有多小？
How little are they?
会不会小得很恐怖？
I mean,are they,like,scary little?
知道吗，我喜欢这种面料
You know, l love this fabric.
我想我应该用这种面料做身衣服
l think l'm gonna have a suit made out of this.
钱德、罗斯，这是劳勃
Chandler,Ross? This is Robert.
你这里沾了唇膏
You have lipstick right here.
没关系，那是我的唇膏 我们刚才接吻了
That's okay,it's mine. We just kissed.
穿短裤有点冷吧？
Isn't it a bit cold out for shorts?
我是加利福尼亚人
Well,I'm from California.
对，有时候你们加利福尼亚人会自燃
Right. Sometimes you guys just burst into flame.
我起来了…我起来了 有人要什么吗？
I'm up. I'm up. I've gotten up now. Anybody want anything?
我要咖啡 我也是
-I'll have coffee. -Me too.
三杯吧
Make that three.
罗斯，跟我来
Ross,why don't you come with me?
怎么了？怎么回事？
What's the matter? What's going on?
劳勃快出来了
Robert's coming out.
什么意思？他是同性恋？
What do you mean? Is he gay?
他就快从短裤里掉出来了
He's coming out of his shorts.
什么？
What?
这家伙暴露重要部位
The man is showing brain.
你确定？等一下
Are you sure? Hold on.
对不起 你们点的是咖啡和…
I'm sorry. That was a coffee and a....
咖啡，我们可以写下来
Coffee. We could write it down.
不…不用了
No,no. That won't be necessary.
怎么样？
Well?
我们该怎么办？…
What do we do? What do we do?
我想只能尽量不要用正眼看
Well,I suppose we just try to not look directly at it.
就像日食一样
Like an eclipse.
如果今晚有人称赞我的手艺 我该怎么说？
When people compliment my cooking tonight,what do I say?
你说“多谢夸奖” 然后给我买漂亮礼物
You say,"Thank you." Then you buy me something pretty.
来，我们把手放进这个碗里…
Come on,we're gonna put our hands in this bowl...
然后开始把番茄压碎
...and we're gonna start squishing the tomatoes.
感觉怪怪的
This feels very weird.
你整天摸人家的眼球 还说这感觉怪怪的？
You touch people's eyeballs and this feels weird?
我当然会摸人家的眼球 但我花了好多年才学着不要压碎它们
Sure,I touch them. But I spent years learning not to squish them.
那是我的手
That's my hand.
继续压 番茄吱吱响
-Keep squishing. -The tomatoes are squishing.
你的衬衫沾到了
You got some on your shirt.
等一下
Hold on a second.
马上放苏打水上去
Just put a little club soda on it. Get to it right away.
应该…
It should do...
就可以了
...the trick.
怎么了？
What?
你裤子上也沾到了
You've got some on your pants.
干脆丢掉算了
I'll just throw them out.
这些小妇人
These little women!
你喜欢吗？
You're liking it?
喜欢，爱美刚烧了乔的稿子
Oh,yeah. Amy just burned Jo's manuscript.
我看他永远不会原谅她
I don't see how he could forgive her.
乔是女的，是乔瑟芬的简称
Jo's a girl. It's short for Josephine.
但乔喜欢劳瑞
But Jo's got a crush on Laurie.
你是说这是女同性恋？
You mean it's like a girl-girl thing?
“闪灵”可没有这种东西
That is the one thing missing from The Shining.
不，其实劳瑞是男的
No,actually,Laurie's a boy.
难怪瑞秋要看这么多次
No wonder Rachel had to read this so many times.
篮球好玩吗？
How'd the basketball go?
我学会了篮板球、罚球 和23分球
I learned how to shoot a lay-up,a foul shot,and a 23-pointer.
你是说三分球吧？
You mean a 3-pointer?
我姿势优美，可以多几分
I get more because I'm dainty.
这里有没有电话可以查留言？
Is there a phone here to check my messages?
在后面，你有铜板吗？ 我一向在袜子里放一个铜板
-ln back. Do you want a quarter? -I always carry one in my sock.
你干嘛？回去那边坐
What are you doing? Get back on your side
喂
Hello!
我是乔伊，我们还没见过面
I'm Joey. We haven't met.
很高兴认识你，劳勃
Good to meet you. Robert.
怎么了？
What?
怎么了？你们怎么回事？
What? You guys,what is going on?
你们不喜欢劳勃吗？
Do you not like Robert?
你们笑什么？
Why are you laughing?
平静一点，用不着激动
Calm down. No reason to get testy.
你们怎么回事嘛？ 对不起
-You guys! Come on! -We're sorry.
只不过你的劳勃的短裤 蔽体的部份…
It just seems that Robert isn't as concealed in the shorts area...
好像是少了一点
...as one may have hoped.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
把饼干拿给我好吗？
Could you pass me those cookies?
没问题
Sure.
-要打球吗（意同“睾丸”）？-是的
-Ball?-Yeah.
他们喜不喜欢意大利面？
So how'd the lasagna go over?
真的？很好 现在你欠我三样礼物了
Really? Good. So you owe me three pretty things.
我一直在想着你的事
I've been thinking about you too.
不，这种柏拉图恋情很不容易
Well,no. It's hard,this "platonomy" thing.
这是一个词
It's a word.
我觉得这样比较好 这样才是明智之举
I do think it's better this way. We're being smart.
对，我肯定
Yes,I'm sure.
你真的肯定？
You really sure?
我稍后再打给你
I'll call you back.
我们可以当有性关系的朋友
So we can be friends who sleep together.
没错，这不代表什么
Absolutely. This'll just be something we do.
就像打壁球一样
Like racquetball.
听起来聪明又健康
Sounds smart and healthy to me.
不过基于好奇心
So just out of curiosity...
你还有几个打壁球的伙伴？
...do you currently have any other "racquetball" buddies?
只有你爸爸一个
Just your dad.
显然那是真的壁球
Although that's actually racquetball.
我下星期二…
You know,I do have a blind date...
要和我妹妹的邻居约会
...with my sister's neighbor next Tuesday.
你希望我取消吗？
Do you want me to cancel it?
不要
No!
如果你取消 那就是为我取消的
Because if you did,that means you'd be canceling for me.
而我们只是朋友 没错
-And we're just friends. -Exactly.
另外，尽管这样不公平
And besides, it wouldn't be fair anyway...
因为我妈妈要撮合我跟律师
...because my mother's trying to set me up with some lawyer.
哪个律师？
So who's this lawyer?
不，她并没有人选，但她一直在寻觅
No, she doesn't actually have one,but she's looking.
不要坐
Oh,don't sit down.
可以走了吗？ 可以
-Ready to go? -You bet.
不过先送你一个礼物
And first,here's a gift.
伸缩内裤？
Stretchy pants?!
世界上最好的东西 如果是我，我会天天穿
The greatest things in the world! If I were you,I'd wear them every day.
谢谢，真的，你太体帖了
Gee,thank you. Really,that's so nice.
不过说老实话 我看我不能穿
But,to be honest,I don't think I can wear these.
这东西太紧了，我会觉得轮廓能被别人看到
They're so tight. I'd feel like I'm on display.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系，我再想办法…
That's all right. I'll figure....
大家好吗？
How's it going?
很好
Good.
“闪灵”好不好看？
How's The Shining?
丹尼刚走进217号房
Danny just went into Room 217.
下面是最精彩的 浴缸里的死女人…
The next part's the best! That dead lady in the bathtub
这样就不好看了
You're gonna ruin it!
我用密码说
I'll talk in code.
记得小孩在走廊 看到那两个“什么”吗？
Remember when the kid sees those two "blanks" in the hallway?
对，那里很好看
Yeah,that's very cool.
所有的“什么”都把 “什么”弄成“什么”
All "blank" and no "blank" makes "blank" a "blank-blank."
不，讲结局
No,the end!
杰克差点用“什么” 杀了他们
Jack almost kills them with the "blank"...
不过到最后关头 他们还是跑了
... but in the last second,they get away.
你居然做这种事
I can't believe you just did that.
她居然识破你的密码
I can't believe she cracked your code.
好，劳瑞跟乔求婚，她拒绝了
Okay. Laurie proposes to Jo and she says no...
虽然她其实爱着他 他后来娶了爱美
...even though she's in love with him. Then he ends up marrying Amy.
我不是存心要讲的
Mine was by accident!
锅炉爆炸，烧毁旅馆 那个爸爸也被烧死了
The boiler explodes and destroys the hotel and kills the dad.
贝丝死了
Beth dies.
贝丝死了？
Beth dies?
真的吗？如果继续看下去 贝丝就会死？
Is that true? If I keep reading,is Beth gonna die?
不，贝丝不会死，她不会死 对不对，瑞秋？
No,Beth doesn't die. She doesn't die. Does she,Rachel?
他问的是你是不是破坏了
He's asking if you've ruined...
他喜欢的第一本不是由杰克尼克尔森（1980年主演《闪灵》） 当主角的小说？
...the first book he's ever loved that didn't star Jack Nicholson.
不，她不会死
No. She doesn't die.
那你干嘛这么说？
Then why would you say that?
因为我故意要伤害你
Because I wanted to hurt you.
在这里，我的钥匙掉了
Oh,there they are. I dropped my keys.
找到了
Got them.
对不起，对不起
Sorry. I'm sorry.
你一定不敢相信我今天有多惨
You would not believe my day.
我上了两个班 除此之外…
I had to work two shifts. And then to top it off...
我的假乳又被烤炉的火烧了
... I lost one of my fake boobs in a grill fire.
你在笑什么？
What are you smiling at?
我在想你可能会遇到好事
I was thinking your day could still pick up.
我喜欢这种朋友关系
I love this "friend" thing!
劳勃马上就要来了 你们哪个人跟他说好吗？
Robert's gonna be here any second,so could one of you just tell him?
拜托，马上说
Please,right now.
我一见他就想“那玩意儿 是不是晃来晃去看着我”
Every time I see him,it's "ls it on the loose? Is it watching me?"
我们不能跟他说
We can't tell him.
你不能跟素昧平生的人 谈他的“那话儿”
You can't go up to a guy you barely know and talk about his "stuff."
他说得对 就算是赞美也不行
He's right. Even if it's to say something complimentary.
你为何不直接跟他说？你要跟他出去
Why don't you just tell him?You're going out with him.
太难了，不，我还从没被允许看那玩意儿
Way too awkward. No. l haven't even seen it with permission yet.
我能做什么？跟他分手？
So, what do l do?Just break up with him?
我不知道，我认为这是个难以解决的问题
l don't know. l think this is an unsolvable problem.
这是个“居里特马瑞”
lt's a curiette mariah.
柯克船长（《星际迷航》）的无法完成的任务
Captain Kirk's unsolvable problem...
是他成为星舰指挥官训练的一部分
...as part of his training to be a Star Fleet commander.
那个训练叫“小林丸”
Kobayashi Maru.
那么“居里特马瑞”是什么？
What's a curiette mariah?
是我们在伊拉克时住的便宜旅馆的名字
lt's the place with the cheap rooms where we stayed in lsrael.
可以去健身了吗？
You ready for the gym?
有一面新的攀岩墙 我们可以互相侦查
There's a new rock-climbing wall. We can spot each other.
我从这里就可以侦查你
Yeah,I can spot you from here.
什么？
What?
听我说，劳勃
Listen,Robert....
我们不是要…
Hey,don't we have to...?
对，我们要
Yeah,we got....
我觉得你这个人真的很棒
I think you're really,really great.
老天，又来了
Oh,God. Here we go again.
为什么老是发生这种事？ 我什么东西让你不高兴？
Why does this keep happening? Is it something I'm putting out there?
这是我的错吗？或者是我傻傻的（与“睾丸”同字）
Is this my fault? Or am I just nuts?
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know what to say.
老弟？这是阖家光临的地方 把老鼠放回屋里去
Hey,buddy? This is a family place. Put the mouse back in the house.
真的？这间公寓很普通啊
Really? It's just like everyone else's apartment.
一样有房间、墙壁和天花板
It's got rooms and walls and ceilings.
我只是想看看你住的地方 带我参观参观
I just wanted to see where you live. Now give me the tour.
我的天
Oh,my God!
这里是客厅 真舒适
-This is the living room. -That's nice.
这里是厨房 真漂亮
-And this is the kitchen. -That's real pretty.
等一下 我不能参观卧室吗？
Wait a minute. Don't I get to see the bedroom?
这是很普通的…
Well,it's pretty much your typical...
卧室
... bedroom.
我们还在门的这一头 我还没看到
We're still on this side of the door. I didn't get to see it.
要命，下次吧 今晚非常愉快
Oh,shoot. Maybe next time. Thanks for a lovely evening.
她是谁？
So who is she?
我跟你说过 就是我妹妹介绍的人
That was the blind date I told you about.
她打电话来改期到今天
She called and switched it from Tuesday.
你喜欢她吗？
Did you like her?
我是以朋友的身份问的 因为我不会不高兴
I'm just asking as a friend,because I am totally fine with this.
你看起来很高兴
Well,you seem fine.
好，你知道吗？ 我不高兴，我很不高兴
Okay,you know what? I'm not fine. I'm not.
我怎么高兴得起来？ 听到你跟她进来
I mean,how could I be fine? Hearing you come in with her.
她还想参观你的卧室
She wants to see your bedroom.
你知道吗？
You know what?
我们或许可以做朋友…
What if we're friends...
但不跟其他人交往
...who don't see other people?
你是说“专属的”朋友？
You mean "exclusive" friends?
有何不可？
Why not?
我是说，这个星期美好极了
I mean,this has been the most amazing week.
这也没什么不好吧
Would it be so terrible?
我们还可以一面做朋友 一面住在一起
Even if we were friends who lived together?
或许有一天 可以站在其他朋友面前
Or maybe someday,friends who stood up in front of their other friends...
发誓当一辈子的朋友
...and vowed to be friends forever.
我们又回到原点了
You know,we're back where we were.
亲爱的，我求之不得 但一切都没有改变
Honey,I would love to do all that,but nothing's changed.
不是这样的 你把胡子刮掉了
That's not true. You don't have a moustache.
好吧，有一件事改变了
Okay,one thing's changed.
但我们生活目标仍不同 我们都知道结局会怎么样
But we still want different things,and we know how this is gonna end.
你知道吗？
You know what?
我得马上离开这个房间
I gotta walk out of here right now.
因为忘记你是我一生中 最不容易的一件事
Because getting over you is the hardest thing I have ever had to do.
我想我再也做不到了
I don't think I could do it again.
我知道我做不到
I know I couldn't.
再打最后一场壁球怎么样？
How about one last game of racquetball?
小心玫瑰刺
Watch the thorns!
怎么了？
What?
贝丝病得很重很重
Beth is really,really sick.
乔在陪她 但我想她也没办法
Jo's there,but I don't think there's anything she can do.
-乔伊，你要把书放在冰箱里吗？-好的 -好的
-Joey，You wanna put the book in the freezer? -Okay -Okay